[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ernest Borgnine debuted on Broadway playing a male nurse in what production?", "correct_answer": "Harvey", "incorrect_answers": ["White Breath", "Annie Get Your Gun", "Road to Hope"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the fate of the fallen in the movie Transformers: Revenge of the Fallen?", "correct_answer": "He is killed.", "incorrect_answers": ["He goes back to the dimension he was previously trapped in.", "He joins the Autobots.", "He overcomes the Autobots."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This movie is about a widower who strives to put his now far-flung family back together. It stars Robert DeNiro, Kate Beckinstale, Drew Barrymore, Sam Rockwell, Ben Schwartz  and  Lucian Maisel.", "correct_answer": "Evrybodys Fine", "incorrect_answers": ["Baby on Board", "Face Value", "In Deep"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After losing his hands in WW2, Homer, one of the main characters in this Oscar-winning movie, tries to push his girlfriend away by demonstrating how difficult life with him would be.", "correct_answer": "The Best Years of Our Lives", "incorrect_answers": ["Marty", "The Apartment", "It happened One Night"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor plays the main character Tony Camonte in the original Scarface movie, directed by Howard Hawks in 1932.", "correct_answer": "Paul Muni", "incorrect_answers": ["Purnell Pratt", "Vince Barnett", "Edwin Maxwell"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Bunad?", "correct_answer": "A Norwegian costume", "incorrect_answers": ["A traditional Norwegian celebration", "A Norwegian song", "A Norwegian meal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie, Over Her Dead Body, an ice sculpture of a lady falls and kills Kate.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of food does Donkey from the Shrek movies like most?", "correct_answer": "Sweets", "incorrect_answers": ["Pizza", "Thistle", "Onions"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What important mineral is sea lettuce especially rich in?", "correct_answer": "Iron", "incorrect_answers": ["Magnesium", "Copper", "Potassium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1981 film was Jack Albertsons final film and included a scene with a dissolving head.", "correct_answer": "Dead  Buried", "incorrect_answers": ["The Aftermath", "Dead Alive", "Waxwork"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Atoms are so small that they can only be observed with a special type of electronic optical microscope called scanning optical microscope.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The trilby is an item which belongs to what clothing group?", "correct_answer": "Hats", "incorrect_answers": ["Dresses", "Shoes", "Pants"]}]